Finding Aid to the Women's Project Theater records SSC.MS.00361
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES I. Plays, 1963-2008; 55.333 linear feet (66 containers)
  - Full Bloom by Suzanne Bradbeer, script, 2002 (Box 18)
  - The Full Lean Years, brochure, undated (Box 18)
  - A Game of Hearts by Joan Vail Thorne, script, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Gateway for Ashes by Dana Leslie Goldstein, script, 1996 (Box 18)
  - Gazebo and Postcards by Carol K. Mack, script, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
  - Sound recordings of Gazebo and Postcards by Carol K Mack, 1982; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 90)
  - Gettysburg by Lisa L. Humbertson, revised script, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
  - Ginger Ale Afternoon by Gina Wendkos, 1988 (Box 18)
  - Girl Bar by Phyllis Nagy, scripts, 1991 (Box 18)
  - The Girl From Clare by PM Cobey, script, 1997 (Box 18)
  - Girl Gone by Jaquelyn Reingold, script, 1980-1999 (Box 18)
  - Girl Under Grain by Karen Hartman, script, 1998 (Box 18)
  - The Glamour House by Lydia Stryk, script, 1999 (Box 18)
  - Gleaning/Rebusca by Caridad Svich, script, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Gloves to Match by Nancy Fairstone, scripts, 1985-1990 (Box 18)
  - God, Sex and Blue Water by Linda Faigao-Hall, script, 1995 (Box 18)
  - God's Pictures by Daisy Foote, scripts, 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Go Go Go by Juliana Francis, script, flyers, program. budget, sales, press, miscellaneous materials, 1991-1997 (Box 18)
  - Goldberg Variations by Marcy Kahan, synopsis and evaluation, 1996 (Box 19)
  - The Good Daughter by Dolores Whiskeyman, rehearsed reading script, 2000 (Box 19)
  - Goodnight Desdemona (Good Morning Juliet) by Ann-Marie MacDonald, script, 1991 (Box 19)
  - The Good Times Are Killing Me by Lynda Barry, script, 1991 (Box 19)
  - Grace by Jane Stanton Hitchcock, script, financial and miscellaneous materials, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Sound recordings of Grace by Jane Stanton Hitchcock, 1981; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 90)
  - The Greatest Day of the Century by Roma Greth, script, program, correspondence, miscellaneous materials, 1979-1983 (Box 19)
  - Sound recordings of The Greatest Day of the Century by Roma Greth, 3 items (3 audiocassettes) (Box 90)
  - Green by Mary Herbert, scripts, responses, 1993-1994 (Box 19)
  - Greensleeves by Joyce Carol Oates, script, 1993-1994 (Box 19)
  - The Guitarron by Lynne Alvarez, script, correspondence, miscellaneous materials, 1979 (Box 19)
  - Sound recordings of Guitarron by Lynne Alvarez, 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 90)
  - Sound recording of The Guitarron show tape, 1 linear feet (1 audio reel-to-reel tape) (Box 97)
  - Gum by Karen Hartman, scripts, playbills, publicity, casting, budget, correspondence, miscellaneous materials, 1998-2000 (Box 19)
  - Sound recordings of Gum by Carole Gilligan, 1999; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 90)
  - Video recording of Gum e-biz segment, 1999; 1 items (One VHS cassette tape) (Box 97)
  - GA Gumbo Primer by Deanna Harris, script, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Hadley's Mistake by Kate Moira Ryan, scripts, 1994 (Box 20)
  - Half Time at Halcyon Days by Carol K. Mack, script, 1983-1984 (Box 20)
  - A Hamlet in Berlin by Terry Galloway, revised script, score, miscellaneous materials, 1984-1986 (Box 20)
  - Happy Endings by Lydia Stryk, script, miscellaneous materials, 1994-1995 (Box 20)
  - Hard Feelings by Neena Beber, script, contracts, casting, publicity, reviews, correspondence, miscellaneous notes and materials, 2000-2001 (Box 20)
  - Sound recordings of Hard Feelings by Neena Beber, 2000; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 92)
  - Harold's Death by Kate Moira Ryan, scripts, 1991 (Box 20)
  - The Harvest by Jean Susan Staniloff, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Hay Devils by Debbie Mitchell, script, flyer, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Haze by France Burke, script, correspondence, miscellaneous materials, 1979-1980 (Box 21)
  - Headshot by Caroline Kava, 1989-1990 (Box 21)
  - Heart of the Dog, a performance piece by Terry Galloway, scripts, notes, budgets, personnel, publicity, spring tour and other miscellaneous materials, 1982-1985 (Box 21)
  - Sound recordings of The Hedda Project by unknown author, 1996; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 92)
  - Hell on Wheels by Mary Lathrop, 1993 (Box 21)
  - Heroes and Saints by Cherrie Moraga, script, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Hey Foxy Mama by Juliette McGinnis Nelson, script, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Sound recordings of Historical Documents by unknown author, 1985; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 92)
  - Holy Places by Gail Kriegel Mallin, scripts, publicity, audience reports, personnel, reviews, miscellaneous materials, 1977-1980 (Box 21)
  - Sound recordings of Holy Places by Gail Kriegel Mallin, 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 92)
  - Hope Lange by Steve Tesich, script, 1980-1999 (Box 21)
  - Horizon Highway by Nancy Grome, script, 1987 (Box 21)
  - Hospice by Pearl Cleage, script, 1979-1990 (Box 21)
  - The House That Goes on Forever by Gretchen Cryer, script, notes,miscellaneous materials, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Box 22)
  - Sound recordings of The House That Goes on Forever by Gretchen Cryer, 11 items (11 audiocassettes) (Box 92)
  - How She Played the Game by Cynthia L. Cooper, script, 1984-1985 (Box 22)
  - I Can't Handle It by Joan Vail Thorne, script with notes, 1979 (Box 22)
  - I Have Often Dreamed of Arriving Alone in a Strange Country by Patricia Cobey, script, 1983-1985 (Box 22)
  - Hunger by Sheri Wilner, script, 1999 (Box 22)
  - Imperceptible Mutabilities in the Third Kingdom by Suzan-Lori Parks, 1988-1994 (Box 22)
  - Incident @ 118th and 2nd Av by Lisa L. Humbertson, script, flyers, 1996 (Box 22)
  - Increase by Brighde Mullins, script, 1988-1999 (Box 22)
  - Ida by Paula Giddings, draft script, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Sound recordings of I Enjoy Being a Girl by an unknown author, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 92)
  - If I Were in Charge of the World, words by Judith Viorst, music by Shelly Markham, script, 1992 (Box 22)
  - Immediate Family by Anna Deveare Smith, script and miscellaneous materials, 1981-1982 (Box 22)
  - Sound recordings of Immediate Family by Anna Deveare Smith, 1982; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 92)
  - Inky by Rinne Groff, program, press packet, review and student study guide packet, 2005 (Box 22)
  - Inside by Susan Kander, scripts with notes, 1992-1993 (Box 22)
  - Intermission by Marjorie Applebaum, script, 1991 (Box 22)
  - In the Heart of America by Naomi Wallace, scripts with notes, 1992-1993 (Box 22)
  - In the Midnight Hour by Kathleen Collins, scripts, correspondence and miscellaneous material, 1994-1998 (Box 22)
  - Sound recordings of In the Midnight Hour by Kathleen Collins, 1980; 3 items (3 audiocassettes) (Box 92)
  - In the Presence by Sallie Bingham, scripts, 1980-1994 (Box 22)
  - Invasions, Incursions, Intrusions, Raids of Love by Susan Flakes, script, 1985 (Box 23)
  - The Itinerary of the Transcendental Signifier by Elizabeth Gould Hemmerdinger, script, 1988-1994 (Box 23)
  - It's Too Late by Taylor Barton, first draft script, 1995 (Box 23)
  - I See My Bones by Kitty Chen, script, program, miscellaneous material, 1994-1995 (Box 23)
  - Jeremiah by Diane Ney, script, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Sound recordings of Joan by Amy Rubin and Eve Merriam, 1 items (1 adiocassette) (Box 92)
  - A Journal of the Plague Year by Cheryl Rouce, script, undated (Box 23)
  - Jump Cut by Neena Beber, flyer, review, student study guide packet and miscellaneous material, 2006 (Box 23)
  - Jun's Swan by E. Katherine Kerr, rehearsed reading script, 2001 (Box 23)
  - Just Outside Miami, Oklahoma by Mary Sue Price, script, 1992 (Box 23)
  - The Key by Joyce Carol Oates, script, flyer, 1990 (Box 23)
  - A Killing Frost by Phyllis Purscell, script, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Killing Time by Ellen MacKay, script, program, miscellaneous material, 1994 (Box 23)
  - Killings on the Last Line by Lavonne Mueller, script, program, miscellaneous materials, 1979-1980 (Box 23)
  - Sound recordings of Killings on the Last Line by Lavonne Mueller, 3 items (3 audiocassettes) (Box 92)
  - Kimchee and Chitling by Elizabeth Wong, script, miscellaneous administrative materials, 1991-1993 (Box 23)
  - The Knee Desires the Dirt by Julie Hebert, scripts, flyers, fundraising, contracts, budgets, correspondence, miscellaneous materials, 1998-1999 (Box 24)
  - A Knife in the Heart by Susan Yankowitz, script with notes, 2001 (Box 24)
  - Knock Off Balance by Cherylene Lee, script, 1995 (Box 24)
  - Kokoro by Velina Hasu Houston, script, 1994
  - Kohoutek by Jane Stanton Hitchcock, script, 1982 (Box 24)
  - Ladies by Eve Ensler, script, program, publicity, reviews, correspondence, casting, miscellaneous materials, 1988-1989 (Box 24)
  - Sound recordings of Ladies by Eve Ensler, 1989; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 92)
  - Ladies in Waiting by Karen Sue Gottlieb and Michele Brourman, correspondence, lyric sheets (Box 25)
  - Lardo Weeping by Terry Galloway, script, miscellaneous matierials, 1991 (Box 25)
  - The Las' Mission O' Boomerang Vestry by Donna Gabel, script, 1984-1985 (Box 25)
  - Last Anniversary by Molly Haskell, scripts, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Last Bus to Mecca by Pearl Cleage, script, 1990 (Box 25)
  - The Last Girl Singer by Deborah Grace Winer, script. budgets, performance reports, correspondence, press, miscellaneous materials, 1994-1995 (Box 25)
  - Sound recordings of The Last Girl Singer by Deborah Grace Winer, 2 items (2 audiocasettes) (Box 92)
  - Sound recording of Last Girl Singer, 4 items (Four MiniDiscs) (Box 97)
  - Last Piece of Flat Land by Alex Finlayson, script, 1984-1988 (Box 25)
  - The Last Word by Barbara Blumenthal Ehrlich, scripts, notes, 1996 (Box 25)
  - The Latecomer by Joan L. Floyd, 1991-1993 (Box 25)
  - Late Night With Lois and Lester by Jarre Fees, script, miscellaneous notes, 1984-1986 (Box 26)
  - Latins in La-La Land by Migdalia Cruz, 1994-1995 (Box 26)
  - Laura Lee and Lareda Getting a Bite to Eat by Lucy Tom Lehrer, script, 1995 (Box 26)
  - Leaning Towards Infinity by Sue Woolfe, scripts, flyers, reviews, miscellaneous materials, 1995-1996 (Box 26)
  - Sound recordings of Leaning Towards Infinity by Sue Woolfe, 1995; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 92)
  - Leaving Queens by Kate Moira Ryan, scripts, score, notes, press, casting, rehearsal, student study guide, workshop and miscellaneous materials, 1995-2001 (Box 26, Box 27)
  - Sound recordings of Leaving Queens by Kate Moira Ryan, 1996-2001; 5 items (5 audiocassettes) (Box 92)
  - The Left Hand Singing by Barbara Lebow, script, 1998 (Box 29)
  - Lemonade by Eve Ensler, script, 1991 (Box 29)
  - Lena by Johann Carlo, script, 1983-1984 (Box 29)
  - Letters to a Daughter From Prison by Lavonne Mueller, script, poster, publicity, correspondence, programs, miscellaneous materials, 1988-1989 (Box 29, Box 98)
    Mounted poster, 15"x20" and flyer, 8 1/2'x11" in flat box 98
  - Letters Home by Rose Leiman Goldemberg, scripts, correspondence, publicity, production, budgets, contracts, program, clippings, 1978-1981 (Box 29)
  - Sound recordings of Letters Home by Rose Leiman Goldemberg, 1979; 4 items (4 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
  - Letters to a Student Revolutionary by Elizabeth Wong, script, 1990 (Box 29)
  - A Life by Steve Tesich, undated (Box 29)
  - Lillian by Migdalia Cruz, scripts, 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Lillian Yuralia by Barbara Eda-Young, script, 2002 (Box 29)
  - Little Castro by Laura Quinn, script, 1994 (Box 29)
  - A Little Going Away Party by Sybille Pearson, script, miscellaneous materials, 1970-1980 (Box 29)
  - Sound recording of A Little Going Away Party by Sybille Pearson, 1978; 3 items (3 audiocassettes) (Box 89, Box 93)
  - Little Joe Monaghan by Barbara Lebow, scripts, miscellaneous materials, 1994 (Box 28)
  - The Little Locksmith by Katharine Butler Hathaway, correspondence, miscellaneous materials, 2002 (Box 28)
  - Little Victories by Lavonne Mueller, scripts, posters, press, budgets, program, correspondence, miscellaneous materials, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Box 98)
    Englarged 1983 New York Times review, 14"x18", mounted on foam board and poster, 15 1/2"x20 1/2", in flat box 98
  - Sound recordings of Little Victories by Lavonne Mueller, 1982; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
  - Living With Mary, undated (Box 28)
  - Lonely Returns from Ambition by Ivey McCray, scripts, 1982 (Box 28)
  - Looking for Jane by Kathleen Conwell Collins, script, 1988 (Box 28)
  - Look What You Made Me Do by Lynda Sturner, script, flyers, 1995 (Box 28)
  - Loose Cannons by Margaret Hunt, scripts, miscellaneous materials, 1990-1993 (Box 28)
  - Loose Knit by Theresa Rebeck, script, 1992 (Box 30)
  - Losing Father's Body by Constance Congdon, script, 1992 (Box 30)
  - Love and Guilt and the Meaning of Life by Judith Viorst, 1991 (Box 30)
  - Luring the Enemy Deep by Lavonne Mueller, script, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Mad as the Blood Sound by Ezzat Goushegir, script, miscellaneous materials, 1992 (Box 30)
  - The Madness of Esme and Shaz by Sarah Daniels, script, 1998 (Box 30)
  - Madonna of the Powder Room by Paula Cizmar, 1981-1982 (Box 30)
  - Magenta Shift by Carol K. Mack, script, 1984-1985 (Box 30)
  - Maggie and Misha by Gail Sheehy, scripts, program, miscellaneous materials, 1990-1991 (Box 30)
  - Making Contact by Patricia Bosworth, scripts with drafts, 1990 (Box 30)
  - Sound recordings of The Marlboro Man by unknown author, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 95)
  - Mapping Uranium by Annie Evans, scripts, program, notes, 1995 (Box 30)
  - Ma Rose by Cassandra Medley, scripts, production, press, budget, correspondence and miscellaneous materials, 1985-1988 (Box 30, Box 31)
  - The Martha Play by Patricia Cobey, script, 1982 (Box 31)
  - Martin Guerre, playwright Laura Harrington, composer Roger Ames, script, 1991 (Box 31)
  - Sound recordings of Martin Guerre by by Laura Harrington, orchestration, 1991; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 93)
  - Maryam's Pregnancy by Ezzat Goushegir, translated by Mansour Bonakdarian, scripts, 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - Masks or Souls by Halide Edib, scripts, 1998 (Box 31)
  - Me and Caesar Lee, music and lyrics by Pat Holley, script, 1996-1997 (Box 31)
  - Sound recordings of Me and Caeser Lee by Pat Holley, 1996-1997; 4 items (4 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
  - Meatless Friday by Brighde Mullins, scripts, 1991
  - A Melting Season by Sharon Houck Ross, scripts, programs, clippings, miscellaneous materials, 1992-1994 (Box 31)
  - Milk of Paradise by Sallie Bingham, scripts, correspondence, publicity, contact sheets, box office reports, miscellaneous materials, 1981-1990 (Box 32)
  - Mill Fire by Sally Nemeth, script including draft, correspondence, advertising, budgets, reviews, contracts, miscellaneous materials, 1987-1990 (Box 32)
  - Millie by Susan J. Kander, script, 1986 (Box 32)
  - Sound recordings of Millie by Susan J. Kander, demo tape, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 93)
  - Miracle Gardening by Marisha Chamberlain, draft script, 1985 (Box 32)
  - Mishuganismo by Susan Nussbaum, draft script, 1991-12 (Box 32)
  - Moe's Lucky Seven by Marlane Meyer, script, 1992-06 (Box 32)
  - Mon General by Lavonne Mueller, script, 1987-1989 (Box 32)
  - Monkey Bones by Bokara Legendre, workshop script, 1994 (Box 32)
  - Monkey in the Middle by Brighde Mullins, rehearsed reading script, 2001 (Box 32)
  - Mortal Sins by Cate Ryan, script, notes, 1990-1992 (Box 32)
  - Mother by Lavonne Mueller, 2001 (Box 32)
  - Mother Necessity by Laura Quinn, script, flyer, 1996 (Box 32)
  - The Mothers (The Mothers of Plaza de Mayo) by Lavonne Mueller, scripts, 1983-1994; 1990 (Box 32, Box 33)
  - Mournin' by Carolyn D. Cole, script, notes, correspondence, miscellaneous materials, 1984 (Box 33)
  - Mourn in Red by Regina Porter, script, 1989 (Box 33)
  - Mud Tracks by Regina Taylor, scripts, 1989 (Box 33)
  - The Mule and the Milky Way by Susan J. Kander, 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Mutiny in the Silence After a Last Sniper by Lavonne Mueller, script, 1982-1983 (Box 33)
  - Sound recording of My Body Works by Taylor Barton, 1992; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 96)
  - My Thing of Love by Alexandra Gersten, script, 1990 (Box 33)
  - My Visits With MGM by Edit Villarreal, script, 1992 (Box 33)
  - My Mother, My Daughter and Me by Gloria Goldsmith, scripts, notes, 1979 (Box 33)
  - Sound recordings of My Mother, My Daughter, and Me by Gloria Goldsmith, 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
  - Nataraj by Elizabeth McDonald, script, 1997 (Box 33)
  - Natural Disasters by Anne Lux, scripts, 1984-1985 (Box 33)
  - Necessary Fictions by Carol K. Mack, 1985-1986; 1990 (Box 33)
  - Next Year in Jerusalem by Dana Leslie Goldstein, scripts, 1993 (Box 33, Box 34)
  - New Jersey Devil by Juliana Franis ("With additional text by Lewis Carroll, Henrik Ibsen and Sylvia Plath"), draft script, flyers, 1998 (Box 34)
  - The New World Monkey by France Burke, script, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1978-1979 (Box 34)
  - Sound recordings of The New World Monkey by France Burke, 1978-1979; 3 items (3 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
  - Niedecker by Kristine Thatcher, scripts, production documents, contracts, programs, notes on sets and miscellaneous materials, 1979-1989 (Box 34)
  - Sound recordings of Night Luster by Laura Harrington, 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 93)
  - Night on Bare Mountain by Patty Gideon Sloan, scripts, correspondence, miscellaneous materials, 1979-1980 (Box 34)
  - Sound recordings of Night on Bare Mountain by Patty Gideon Sloan, 1979; 3 items (3 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
  - Night Sky by Susan Yankowitz, script, program, correspondence, budget, box office reports, miscellaneous materials, 1979-1991 (Box 34, Box 35)
  - Floppy Disks of Night Sky, 3 items (Three floppy disks) (Box 97)
  - Nobody's Business by Penelope Gilliatt, script, 1970-1980 (Box 35)
  - No Dessert for You, My Friend by Michael angel Johnson, 1988-1989 (Box 35)
  - No More Chattanooga Choo Choo by Sally Ordway, script notes, miscellaneous materials, 1975-1985 (Box 35)
  - Sound recordings of No More Chattanooga Choo Choo by Sally Ordway, 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
  - Sound recording of No More Chatanooga Choo Choo by Sally Ordway and Sound recording of Death of a Miner by Paula Cizmar, 1981; 1 items (1 audio reel-to-reel tape) (Box 97)
  - Noonday Sun by Cassandra Medley, scripts, 1998-1999 (Box 35)
  - No Such Thing by Lisa Dillman, script, 2001 (Box 35)
  - Notes from a Wife by Taylor Barton, script, 1988-1999 (Box 35)
  - Sound recordings of Notes from a Wife by Taylor Barton, 1992; 1 items (1 audiocassette) (Box 93)
  - Not Waving by Gen LeRoy, script, 1991 (Box 35)
  - Notes on a Life music and lyrics by Janet Neipris, 1986 (Box 35)
  - Nothing Immediate by Shirley Lauro, script, 1984-1985 (Box 35)
  - The Object of Your Desire by Maryrose Wood, scripts, notes, 1993-1994 (Box 35)
  - Off the Ice by Barbara Field, scripts, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1989 (Box 35)
  - Okiboji by Elizabeth Fuller and Conrad Bishop, scripts, 1988-1992 (Box 37)
  - The Old Maid by Zoe Atkins, script, marketing, casting and miscellaneous materials, 1992-1994 (Box 37)
  - Old Man River by Cynthia Gates Fujikawa, scripts, notes, flyers, miscellaneous materials, 1994-1995 (Box 37)
  - The Old Matador by Milcha Sanchez-Scott, draft script, 1994 (Box 37)
  - Old Wives Tale by Julie Jensen, script, 1982 (Box 37)
  - On Common Ground by Gail Kriegel, script, 1982-1983 (Box 37)
  - Only Angels by Katharine Houghton, scripts, 1998 (Box 37)
  - The Only Woman General by Lavonne Mueller, script an poster, 1983-1984 (Box 37, Box 98)
    Poster, 17"x22", in flat box 98
  - Sound recording of The Only Woman General song Kill a Commie for Christ, 1 items (One audio reel-to-reel tape) (Box 97)
  - Sound recording of The Only Woman General, 2 items (Two audio reel-to-reel tapes) (Box 97)
  - On the Home Front by Gail Kriegel, script rewrite, 1983-07-07 (Box 37)
  - O Pioneers! by Willa Cather, adapted by Darrah Cloud, draft and final scripts, production notes, programs, correspondence, budgets, miscellaneous materials, 1989-2000 (Box 35, Box 36)
  - Video recording of O Pioneers!, 1 items (One VHS cassette tape) (Box 97)
  - The Other Side of Newark by Enid Rudd, script, 1983-1984 (Box 37)
  - Our Place in Times by Clare Coss, scripts, research reports, design information, casting, contracts, ticket sales, miscellaneous materials, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Box 38)
  - Out of Season by Elinor Jones, script, 1999 (Box 38)
  - Over a Barrel by BeatriceTerry, script, 2001 (Box 38)
  - Owl Attacks by Serret Scott, script, 1994 (Box 38)
  - Paducah by Sallie Bingham, script, publicity, flyers, program, corres;pondence, clippings, miscellaneous materials, 1980-1985 (Box 38)
  - Pandora and the Boxscript by Neena Beber, script, 1995 (Box 38)
  - Paper Dolls by Elaine Jackson, script, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1980 (Box 38)
  - Sound recordings of Paper Dolls by Elaine Jackson, 1981; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
  - Paper Wings by Joanne Pollitzer, scripts, 1988-1990 (Box 38)
  - Sound recordings of Paper Wings by Joanne Pollitzer, "Lament" and "Viva La Vida" composed by Francisco Gonzalez, 1988; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 93, Box 94)
  - Parataxis by Wendy Belden, scripts with notes, 1994-1995 (Box 38)
  - The Parting of the Ways by Corinne Jacker, script, 1970-1990 (Box 39)
  - Parting Kind by Alma Becker, script, 1985-1986 (Box 39)
  - The Passion of Claire by Cheryl Royce, script, 1999 (Box 39)
  - The Past Master by Lionel Shriver, script, notes, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Sound recordings of The Past Master by Lionel Shriver, 1982; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
  - Peacetime by Elaine Berman, script, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Pearls on the Moon by Shirley Lauro, script, 1984-1985 (Box 39)
  - Penelope by Sophy Burnham, script, miscellaneous materials, 1970-1979 (Box 39)
  - Sound recordings of Penelope by Sophy Burnham, 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
  - Pennie Before the Holidays by Lissa Benyon, script, clippings, miscellaneous materials, 1978-1986 (Box 39)
  - Personality by Gina Wendkos and Ellen Ratner, script, flyers, publicity, 1990 (Box 39)
  - Sound recording of Personality, 1986; 1 items (One audio reel-to-reel tape) (Box 97)
  - Phaedra in Delirium by Susan Yankowitz, scripts, Playbills, budgets, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1979-1998 (Box 39)
  - The Pharmacist's Daughter by Monika, Monika, script, 1998 (Box 40)
  - Philomena's Tapestry by Alice Eve Cohen, scripts, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1993 (Box 40)
  - The Piano House by Lissa Benyon, script, 1989 (Box 40)
  - Pidgin' Hole (A Satire) by Linda Faigao Hall, script, flyer, program, 1996 (Box 40)
  - Piggyback by Sallie Bingham, script, 1982 (Box 40)
  - Plantation by Velina Hasu Houston, draft script, 1991-09 (Box 40)
  - Poets' Corner by Eliza Wyatt, script, 1981 (Box 40)
  - The Poker Game by Susan Brownmiller, scripts, draft and final, 1990 (Box 40)
  - Portraits by Michael angel Johnson, script segment, undated (Box 40)
  - Postcards by Carol K. Mack, script, 1981-1982 (Box 40)
  - The Prevaricated Life History of Constance O'Malley by Caroline Kava, correspondence, publicity, budgets, personnel and miscellaneous materials, 1981 (Box 40, Box 98)
    Graphic artists mock-up of poster, on board, 15"x20", in flat box 98
  - The Price of Madness by Catherine Filloux, scripts, program, 1991 (Box 40)
  - Primagravida by Pamela Blafer Lack, 1985-1986 (Box 40)
  - Private Fudge in the Killing Zone by Lavonne Mueller, script, 1985 (Box 40)
  - Promenade, book and lyrics by Maria Irene Fornes, Music by Al Carmines; script, 1988-1994 (Box 40)
  - Property by Penelope Gilliatt, 1970-1980 (Box 40)
  - Quotations From Other Lives by Penelope Gilliatt, script, correspondence, notes, miscellaneous materials, 1970-1980 (Box 40)
  - Sound recordings of Quotations from Other Lives by Penelope Gilliatt, 1979; 2 items (2 audiocassettes) (Box 93)
  - The Rats of Whifflisburg by Patricia Green, script, 1994 (Box 40)
  - Real Estate by Michele A. Miller, script with draft, 2002 (Box 40)